Hey! Ichi!
Oh! I knew you'd be here, Ichi!
I looked everywhere for ya.
Huh? You in the middle of somethin'?
I'm saved!
I almost lost my mind back there!
Don't worry about it.
What's up?
Oh, right, right. What's her name?
You know, that third-year girl?
The really cute one?
Cute...?
Oh yeah, Kikukawa-senpai!
You had plans to hang out with
her after school today, right?
You left her on read, so
I had to come and look for you like—
Sentaro!
Huh?
Th-The Prince?!
Yoi-chan.
Please don't pull this kind
of thing on me ever again.
H-Huh? Th-The P-Pri—?!
Well then, good-bye.
Huh, what?!
Seriously, what's goin' on?!
He's the Prince, after all.
He must be very popular indeed.
"Cute," my ass.
I knew he was saying it to everyone.
There's no way I'm getting
fooled by those cheap words.
Curry Diner
Nasu Oyaji Curry
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh ho, you got those roses flying
again today, huh, Yoi-chan?
Must be nice.
I want some of those, too.
Yoi, can you handle the register?
Yeah.
Um, excuse me, but you're...
a girl, right?
Oh, yes.
Really?! Oh wow!
I bet you're always being told how
handsome you are, aren't you?
The Prince is so handsome.
Such a hottie.
Cute.
You're just cute, Yoi-chan.
I know he's probably
saying it to everyone.
But that was a first for me...
To be called "cute" by a boy.
Oh, welcome... in.
Yo.
Wh-What're you doing here?!
Wait, are you really stalking me?!
You forgot this.
Huh?
Is it okay if I get some curry?
Two customers coming in.
Whoa!
Hey, looks good!
You guys are from Yoi's school, right?
I'll bump the size up for you two.
Seriously?!
Thanks so much.
Why are you telling everyone
that we run a curry place?
I didn't tell anyone. He figured it out.
That's... That's...!
That's the place in the
curry restaurant hot spot
that sells curry, coffee, and records!
The novelty store, Nasu Oyaji Curry, right?!
He's a hardcore curry fanatic.
R-Right...
Thank you for the meal!
And? Which one is your boyfriend?
Dad, please.
Well, you know.
The only men I've ever seen you
speak to are me and our patrons.
I've never heard you speak about
any favorite actors or idols.
That's why I'm relieved to see
you actually talking to boys
the same age as you.
It crossed my mind before,
but he really does look like
he enjoys his food while he eats...
Oh, not good. I'm staring again.
So strange.
Phew, I'm stuffed.
Man, I'm seriously startin' to doze.
Well, I wanna wrap up this review,
so I'm headin' home!
Let's see... Let's see...
Right! Here's the money, and this is
my social media account for curry!
Sentaro Akane
Thanks for today, Prince!
The food was great, Boss!
Right, thank you!
Um, your friend went home, you know.
Hmm, just a little bit longer...
What is he, drunk?
Yoi-chan.
When do you get off work?
I want to walk you home.
I can't just... leave work like that.
Yoi, you're good for today!
I'll clock you out.
What?! Wh-Why would you...?
Don't worry about it!
Just be home by nine, okay?
Why is this happening?!
Jeez... Are you not worried
about your own daughter?
You guys are tight.
It's a nice store. Your curry place.
Th-Thanks.
So, um... how did your thing go, Senpai?
Hanging out after school...
Oh, I passed.
What? Wh-Why?!
No reason. I wasn't really
into it to begin with.
Besides, it was more important
to deliver the thing you left behind.
Y-You could have done that any other time!
It's not good to break a promise you made
to a woman over something like that.
Something funny?
I was just thinking...
you're such a prince, as always.
Hey, I'm sorry.
About lunch today.
I didn't realize you were annoyed,
so I came to properly apologize.
But it looks like
I just made you upset again.
So, I'm sorry.
When he just apologizes like that, I...
No, I wasn't mad or anything.
Even at lunch today, I wasn't angry
because I was bothered...
More like...
Huh? How should I put...
What?
Aw, seriously?
We should find cover.
Yoi-chan.
Can you run?
Huh? H-Hey...
What is this place?
Hey, you can't just—
It's all right. I live here.
You're gonna catch a cold,
so come in.
H-Hey... What's going on?!
Here, something to change into.
Sorry, it's just some of my old clothes.
The bathroom is out
and to the left, okay?
U-Um, Senpai, what exactly
is this house of yours?
Oh, my grandpa is president of a company.
P-President...
Come to think of it, I think Nobara
said something similar, too.
Even so, he doesn't have
that kind of presence.
He just had a normal bread
roll for lunch, too.
I wonder why.
Um, thank you for the clothes.
It just naturally looks good on you, huh?
I like that about you, Yoi-chan.
I'm just kiddin'.
I'll get us some tea.
Looking over it again,
this place is really something...
And... are we the only ones here?
So this is what they meant
when they called you a prince.
Yeah. Stupid, isn't it?
Calling me a prince because
my family is rich is just dumb.
Seasoned Seaweed
I don't care that they say it,
but it's a real bother when
it draws unwanted attention.
Seasoned Seaweed
That's why at school I try
to keep it on the DL.
I-I see.
Maybe he has his own set of problems, too?
That senpai I declined
today is that exact type.
The whole "promise" was something
she just decided for me, too.
You can just tell when
they're gonna be like that.
If that's the case, then I...
It's not good to break a promise you made
to a woman over something like that.
U-Um...
I'm sorry for scolding you
when I didn't have the full picture.
Come on, you don't gotta
apologize like that.
And like I said, I was already
putting you in a tough spot, so...
Well... I wouldn't say that...
I'm really just not used to
interacting with men.
And I didn't want you to find that out,
so it all came out sounding cold...
It's the first time a man has
ever approached me like that.
I'm just not sure how to handle it.
I'm sorry.
And this?
You okay with this?
Huh? Why... can't I move?
Oh, yes, yes! Picking up right now!
Incoming Call
Dad
No way, it's already this late?!
I'm sorry! I have to go.
Yoi-chan.
I'll take you home.
Um, I won't tell anyone
about your house...
Oh, it's all good.
We rent a place
elsewhere to act as a decoy.
Though it's a condo registered
under my grandpa's name.
S-Such entitlement...
Is it really okay for you
to be telling me all this?
With you, it's fine.
Even if you wanted to kill me,
I'd let it happen.
Isn't it kind of nice that
the last thing I'd get to see
would be something so beautiful?
Don't you think you're
laying it on a bit thick?
Nah, I was just kiddin'.
You gotta call me out,
or I really sound crazy, y'know?
Well, I'll take it from here.
Are you sure you don't want
me to walk you halfway?
That makes me taking you
home pointless, yeah?
Take care, Senpai.
Kohaku.
Kohaku Ichimura.
That's my name.
I previously said my feelings for
you were "different from love."
But I take that back.
I think it's pretty close.
Well then, see ya tomorrow.
Just when I think I've
figured him out,
he slips through my fingers and
becomes something else.
He's like the reflection
of the moon on the water.
Kohaku. Kohaku Ichimura.
In spite of myself, I started thinking,
"That's a nice name."
And?
What's going on with you
and Ichimura-senpai?
Huh... Oh.
What do you mean, "Oh?"
We're gonna make you
spit it all out!
No way!
Ichimura-senpai is hitting on you?!
I wouldn't say he's hitting on me...
More like, he kind of follows me around...
That's still amazing!
The orthodox Prince and the assertive,
unconventional Prince, huh?
It's all coming together!
Hey, now.
You know, I am a girl.
Still, for someone who's shy and
inexperienced in love like you, Yoi-chan,
maybe someone who's assertive and
experienced is better?
I-It's not like that!
Besides, I don't do well with
people like that to begin with.
Get serious!
The initial dislike just makes it spicier
down the line, Prince Takiguichi!
Yep. Yep.
But I heard Ichimura-senpai was
pretty indifferent towards girls,
so it's surprising.
I-Is that so?
Yeah. So it might be that when
it comes to you, Yoi-chan.
"That"?
You know... like fate!
N-No, no, it's definitely not!
You sure?
You never know!
I mean...
My image of him has changed a lot
from my first impression...
And I'm starting to understand
that he isn't all that bad.
Still, saying it's "fate"...
That's jumping the gun, don't you think?
Besides, I'm not even sure
how serious he is...
Hey, isn't that the prince?!
What, really?
Prince!
Kohaku!
I heard you stood up Kikukawa-senpai
the other day. That true?
Uh, yeah.
Come hang out with us, then.
Huh? I've been pretty busy lately.
Oh, I know!
It's about the first-year
Prince that he's totally into!
What, for real?! Did he change types?
Right?! She's pretty and all,
but that's a nuh-uh from me.
'Cause she's totally a guy
at first glance! Right?
Right?
You guys are looking
pretty ugly right now.
Didja know that?
What an ass. Let's go!
Oh, man, that was pretty harsh.
Why? It's the truth.
You know, I've been thinking
this for a while,
but you're pretty cold towards
girls, aren't you, Ichi?
Isn't that normal?
Actually, I was wondering the same thing.
Why are you so obsessed
with the first-year Prince?
I was wondering that, too!
She's the total opposite
of the girls you usually date.
Seriously? I'm wondering why
everyone else isn't interested.
First of all, she looks like that
but she's a girl, right?!
That alone makes you
super curious, doesn't it?
Like how she usually acts, or how she
acts when she's talking to a guy,
or what's it like if she
takes off her clothes...
That's sexual harassment, right there!
Come on, that's just you being horny!
Huh?
Man, I thought it was unusual for
you to be making the first move, Ichi.
It's just impure thoughts motivating you.
Impure, huh.
Huh? Where are you going?
Skipping class.
You're gonna have to repeat a year.
Princes don't repeat years.
Yes they do!
Seriously, though.
Why isn't anyone else curious?
For something that beautiful,
anyone would stop and stare for sure.
Wouldn't anyone want it?
How can a desire to know more about it,
to have it, be impure? Isn't it natural?
So weird.
What's wrong?
I suddenly got the chills...
Are you okay?
I'll just go to the nurse's
office and get some medicine.
Okay.
Th-That's not entirely true.
Actually, I've had a slight
fever since this morning.
I can feel it rising.
It's probably from that.
For now, I'll just get something
to reduce the fever and—
Hey, it's Yoi-chan.
That's pretty low, don't ya think?
You didn't have to slam the door.
Please let go.
I really don't want to
deal with you right now.
Hey, you don't look okay.
You good?
Is it a cold?
I'm fine.
I'll be all right on my own, so...
Please leave me be.
Just ask for help when you're down, yeah?
You don't have to be a prince
in front of me, y'know.
Thanks.
You good? Can you stand?
Please don't worry... about me.
For now, just lie down for a bit.
I'll get the teacher.
Sorry for the trouble...
He's really never done
anything that bad...
I'm the one who's just not being honest.
Sorry, the teach's out.
Why are you getting in?!
I thought you might
need someone to keep you warm.
Like a co-sleeping thing.
Well, I don't! Please get out!
See, what'd I tell ya?
This guy...
Hey, jokes aside, come closer.
I'm not gonna do anything.
Absolutely not.
Hmm... Then I'll get closer.
H-Hey, what are you—!
It's okay, it's okay, rest time.
If only I had my strength back...
I told you.
Rely on me a little.
Trust me a bit, will ya?
I'm not that desperate, y'know?
Once I'm better, you're
gonna pay for this.
Yeah, yeah. Once you're better,
feel free to do whatever you want.
You should've stayed home if you
had a fever in the first place.
I've never been absent from school, so...
No way. Not even once?
Nope.
For real? You're seriously
a model student.
A different scent from a girl's...
You're warm.
Senpai...
My body temperature's naturally high.
Makes me cute like a cat, right?
Cats are...
cute.
Man, we slept so long.
We slept too long!
What should I do?
I skipped sixth period!
You weren't going to make it
with that fever anyway.
Still!
How's the fever?
Feelin' sluggish?
I think I'm feeling much better now.
Okay. Then I'll take you home.
What?
I'll get my stuff.
Um... But...
Huh? My bag...
Yoi-chan,
You didn't come back,
so we came to check on you, and oh my what a sight.
I'll just leave your things here.
We want to hear the deets tomorrow, okay?
Kotobuki
You didn't come back, so we came to
check on you, and oh my what a sight.
I'll just leave your things here.
You guys sure were sound asleep
Nobara
You guys sure were sound asleep.
We want to hear the deets tomorrow, okay?
What am I even doing?
Say, I'm starving.
You wanna grab something to eat?
No. I'm heading straight home.
Oh, all right.
Hey, the curry at your place, Yoi-chan—
I'm not going there.
Hey, there's a delicious looking diner.
Not going in.
You're no fun.
I'm starting to get used to
going home with this guy...
Boy, did I sleep.
You're real comfortable
to sleep with, Yoi-chan.
There you go sounding
like a creep again.
Nah, I'm serious.
Isn't it important to find
someone comfy to sleep with?
How should I know?
Y'know, they say that's how
you know who your soulmate is.
You know... like fate!
Everyone is so quick to say
it's fate, it's fate...
Does that... even really exist?
How would you even confirm it?
Then...
You wanna try going out?
To experiment?
I'm not just getting used to it...
I'm gradually being corrupted by it.
I think it's pretty close.
I wonder how serious he was about that.
Just kidd—
All right.
Then, would you like to try going out?
The Evening Downpour and the Cat
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis